

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

# **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and -builder of human happiness. No one r of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

# **EDUCATION**



### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. y can send your design review off the rails." And that's administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

### **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

# **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult bạn có thể tìm thấy, nhưng đa số được biến đổi bằng cách thê and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

# Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and
- Assist to etter-by-letter resetting but even the leap into ele goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

# ACTIVITIES



Sep 2003 - 2007

# **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer se those who do not know how to pursue pleasure r' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

# **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

# HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO

2013 - 2014

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US ved not only five centuries, but also the leap into electronic typesetting, remaining esse

# **REFERENCES**



# **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

# **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop

Excel English

Power Point Japanese

# **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt molestiae and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities